Hush ( 2016 ) bluray SDH ASL removed for use with hardsub ASL Overlapping lines positioned at top of screen
[ clicking ]
[ sound fades out ]
[ message tone ]
[ rattling ]
[ cat meows ]
[ meows ]
Hi .
I finished your book .
I know you can read my lips ,
but I am getting better .
Better .
I um ... I want to practise .
Taking another class with John .
It 's fun !
I am way better at understanding it than actually doing it , but ...
What did I ... What did I think ?
I loved it .
I um ...
I loved Riley .
I loved Erin .
They were great characters .
I tried to guess the ending .
I am usually on point with that sort of thing , but I was way off !
How did you do that ? How do you ... ?
How do you come up with that ?
[ laughs ]
A voice ?
Does the voice sound like a kid ?
You were 13 when you got sick ?
Whatever is going on in your brain ,
I think that you are a good storyteller .
What ?
[ laughs ]
Well , I 'm sure you 're also a lovely kisser .
[ alarm blares ]
[ sound fades out ]
[ sound fades in , alarm blares ]
[ meows ]
[ alarm stops ]
Jesus !
God ! That is one hell of a fire alarm !
Well , I imagine that would wake anyone .
Oh ! Cat ?
She 's a ... She 's a what ?
[ laughs ]
Bitch .
[ pats leg ]
I am sorry about dinner .
Do you want to come over ?
We can order in and watch a movie .
John will be home in an hour , so he can join .
I understand .
Thank you for ... for letting me borrow this .
Thank you .
I 'll pop by tomorrow and brush up signs ?
I 'm going to get good .
I 'm determined .
- Kissing . - Kissing .
Storyteller .
Bitch .
[ message tone , vibrating ]
[ sighs ]
[ female voice ] ... clenching the book
Riley to the church .
The church to Erin .
The church to Father Paul .
Bring in Erin . Scratch that . Try this .
The rage bubbled up , spreading into his head .
His ears rang . His eyes felt hot .
She 's happy .
... mysterious ways .
Nope , not working .
Not working . Something brighter .
... looking down with her wide , endlessly patient eyes .
They would twinkle with red , blue and yellow light ,
just as the damned Jesus fish had
when it pulled him out of the fog and into hell .
That 's better .
It needs something more , something better .
Erin dies . Can 't kill Erin . That would piss ' em off . Didn 't set it up properly .
Or scrap the whole book and find another career .
A better idea .
[ voice fades out ]
[ sighs ]
[ ringing ]
[ phone continues ringing ]
[ ringing stops ]
[ screams ] Maddie !
Maddie , please see me !
[ pounds on door ]
Maddie , please help me !
[ sound fades out ]
Maddie ! [ cries out ]
[ cries out ]
No !
[ yells ] No !
[ gasps ]
[ cries out ]
[ door rattles ]
[ phone ringing , vibrating ]
[ ringing stops ]
[ door opening , typing ]
[ knife blade tapping ]
[ tapping continues ]
[ ringing ]
Hey , Squish .
What are you up to ?
Going that well , huh ?
[ Max laughs ]
Are you still stuck on the ending ?
Glad I could distract you .
Talk about bad endings ! Did you talk to him ?
It 's been a year !
Mom keeps asking when you 're getting back out there .
Look at you !
Miss the city yet ?
Seriously , Maddie ?
Maybe you could come back .
Live with me .
I worry about you .
It is not good for anyone to be alone , Squish .
Isolating yourself the way that you do ...
Who was that ?
Behind you . I thought I saw something move .
I love you .
[ rattling ]
[ cat food rattling ]
[ sighs ]
[ typing ]
[ message tone ]
[ panting ]
[ thumps door ]
[ lock turns ]
[ glass screeches ]
[ sound fades out ]
[ air hisses ]
Can you read my lips ?
Can you ?
You have seen it now , haven 't you ?
" Seriously , Maddie .
Maybe you could come back and live with me . "
" You know , I worry about you .
It 's not good for anyone to be so alone , Squish . "
I can come in any time I want .
And I can get you any time I want .
But I 'm not going to .
Not until it 's time .
When you wish you are dead -
that 's when I 'll come inside .
Do you understand me ?
Nod your head if you understand me .
Good .
Then we can have some fun .
Enjoy it .
[ panting ]
[ grunts ]
[ banging on window ]
[ banging continues ]
[ panting ]
[ gasps ]
[ alarm blares ]
[ lock turns ]
[ alarm continues ]
[ gasps , panting ]
[ alarm stops ]
[ man cries out ]
[ man grunts ]
[ man screams ]
[ lock turns ]
[ whimpers ]
[ cries out ]
[ man groans ]
[ groans ]
[ sound fades out ]
[ panting ]
[ approaching footsteps ]
[ pounding on glass ]
[ panting ]
[ heavy footsteps ]
[ light footsteps ]
[ departing footsteps ]
[ panting ]
[ crossbow fires ]
[ tapping ]
[ guttering creaks ]
[ crossbow fires ]
[ panting ]
[ grunts ]
[ man cries out ]
[ groans ]
[ panting ]
[ bangs head ]
[ lock turns ]
[ whimpers ]
[ gasps , panting ]
[ sobs ]
[ gasps ]
[ thumps floor ]
[ panting ]
[ sobs ]
[ gasps , panting ]
[ crossbow bolt rattles ]
[ bow straining ]
Not so easy , is it ?
Sarah ?
- [ intruder ] On the ground ! - [ neighbour ] Whoa !
[ intruder ] On the ground . Drop it !
- It 's just a phone . - Drop it ! Hands behind your head .
- Take it easy . I 'm a friend . - Hands where I can see ' em .
I don 't want any trouble . Just do what I say .
My name is John Stanley .
- I said , " On your knees , " sir . - OK !
I 'm a neighbour , just looking for my girlfriend .
- Show me some ID . - It 's in my wallet , OK ? Take it easy .
- Hands where I can see ' em . - I 'm just gonna go for my wallet .
I 'm gonna put my phone down and reach for my wallet . Take it easy .
- You live next door ? - Yes , sir .
OK .
I am sorry to scare you .
There has been a ...
Phew !
Jesus ! Um ...
- What the hell happened here ? - I don 't know . Um ...
I responded to a call .
I got here and found the place like this . There was someone inside .
He came running past me and knocked me cold .
I woke up without my phone , my gun or my radio .
I need to call for backup .
- Do you know who lives here ? - Yeah , it 's Maddie .
Maddie Young . She 's a friend of ours .
Does she live alone ?
Yeah . My girlfriend comes here all the time . I thought maybe ...
What is her name ?
It 's Sarah . Sarah Greene .
OK . Sarah . I 'm sorry . Can I use your phone to call for backup ?
I should have called it in already ,
but I just started this job , and when I got here ...
- Are you police ? - Deputy . Just barely , though .
I can call the Sheriff , if I can just use your ... ?
Here you go .
Thanks .
Yeah , I got a 7-19 here at 811 Fairhope .
Signs of possible forced entry . Suspect is at large on foot .
No one else here , but a neighbour just showed up .
Yeah . OK .
See you soon .
Hey , did you see that ?
Yeah , I did .
This girl , Maddie , does she have a boyfriend ?
No , I don 't think so .
Hm .
Family nearby ? Anybody else that could possibly have access to the house ?
No , she pretty much keeps to herself .
- Is your arm OK ? - Oh , yeah .
The guy just ploughed into me . He hit me like a truck .
He must have been ... well , just about your size , actually .
You know , like a jock .
Linebacker type .
Scary guy .
Can I get that back ?
The phone .
Oh !
[ chuckles ]
Yeah , of course . Sorry .
So stupid of me . Force of habit .
You said you responded to a call . Was that from Maddie ?
From the dispatcher ... actually .
They said someone had called it in . I just assumed it was the resident .
Yeah , because she wouldn 't be able to make that call . She 's deaf and mute .
Huh .
Well , I guess it must have been your girlfriend who made the call .
[ panting ]
[ bow straining ]
[ gasps ]
[ panting ]
[ crossbow clatters ]
So , deaf mute , huh ?
Pretty rough .
Has she always been unable to hear ?
No , not always .
Since she was a teenager , I think . Meningitis .
Still , to live alone like this ... she must be able to get by .
I can 't swear to it , but
I 'm pretty sure she has a spare key in that planter on the porch down there .
Wouldn 't that be great ?
Yeah .
Just ... ?
Yeah , it 's right down there , on that corner .
So , who do you think it was ?
Like , a burglar ?
- I hope it wasn 't something worse . - I am sure they are fine .
If they called it in , they probably got the hell out of here .
Trashed her car pretty good , huh ?
[ intruder ] Oh , yeah . Look at that . Jeez !
So , how long do you think it will take for the cavalry to arrive ?
About ten . Fifteen , maybe .
Really ?
I 'm glad you happened across me . I could have been out here all night , bleeding .
Yeah , I 'm glad I came by .
In here , you said ?
Yeah , I think so . I 'm not sure .
[ banging ]
Easy .
Hey , hey , hey !
Hey , come on . It is done . It is done .
It is done .
[ John cries out ]
I figured I had about a two-in-ten chance if it came to a fight .
You are just so damn big .
[ John gasps ]
I 'm actually pretty glad she showed up when she did . Thank you .
Shh ! It 's OK . It 's OK . It 's OK .
[ grunting ]
[ intruder chokes ]
Run !
You can 't run .
[ voice echoes ]
[ intruder wheezes , John gargles ]
[ intruder gasps ]
[ female voice ] You can 't run . You can 't run .
You can 't outrun him on that leg .
- I can 't outrun him on that leg . - The crossbow has to be a perfect shot .
In the heart or in the brain .
Anything else is not gonna cut it .
Perfect shot .
And that 's a long-distance weapon .
It 's useless indoors .
It 's really tough up close , and you would have to be close to land a kill shot .
He will be moving .
You can 't even figure out how to load it .
- Go outside . - Get the power back on .
Go outside . Get the power back on .
He could have flipped a switch or cut the wires .
- Hiding . - Hiding .
Bedroom , bathroom , loft .
Windows in each . All he needs is a rock .
All he needs is a rock .
The loft has no cover , no doors to barricade .
Best-case scenario , he doesn 't find you and you bleed to death .
... doesn 't find me and I bleed to death .
- Outside . - Head outside .
- Crawl space . - Go back outside .
- Crawl space . - The crawl space .
- I tried that once . - He knows you tried that .
There is little room to manoeuvre . If he figures out you are there ...
If he figures out I 'm there ...
I don 't think you will last that long .
- I don 't think I will last that long . - You are cold , dizzy , and you 're sweaty .
Your fingernails are blue . Your vision is fading .
We are running out of time !
How long before you can 't even walk , or stand up , or see ?
Sooner or later , he is coming in here .
He knows I am bleeding out .
Once he is in this house , it is over .
He is bigger , stronger and faster .
And he has got the advantage .
He has the advantage .
He can hear you .
I can 't run .
I can 't hide .
And we can 't wait .
You go outside , you are dead .
Too many endings .
They are all the same .
All the same .
Which means there is only one ending he won 't expect .
Ending ...
If you can 't run , hide , or wait
what does that leave ?
Yeah ... I never would have won that fight .
Oh , John , John , John .
These things will kill you .
What do you think , John ?
Hm ?
Should I go in there ... and get this over with ?
Yeah .
You 're probably right .
I should wait a while longer
until she has lost more blood .
I don 't want to tempt a shot
in case her aim is any better than her judgement .
[ meows ]
Oh , hey there !
Hey .
Is this your house ?
Does your mommy live there ?
Let 's check .
Aww !
Welcome home , puss .
It 's OK . You 're gonna see Mommy very soon .
Or , at least , she will see you
nailed to the front ...
[ cries out ]
[ groans ]
[ gasps ]
[ bones crunch ]
[ bones cracking ]
[ lock turns ]
[ sobbing ]
I 'm coming in .
[ typing ]
[ lock turns ]
You know what ?
I think that you 're holding out on me .
I bet if I hit the right spot
I can make you scream .
[ man screams ]
You fucking cunt .
[ cries out ]
[ groans ]
[ alarm blares , man yells ]
[ sound fades out ]
[ sound fades in , alarm blares ]
[ man grunts ]
[ man cries out ]
[ impact thuds ]
[ sound fades out , thudding heartbeat ]
[ slowing heartbeat ]
[ sound fades in , alarm blares ]
[ Maddie wheezes ]
[ man groans ]
[ man splutters , gasps ]
[ Maddie wheezes ]
[ man groans , Maddie wheezes ]
[ Maddie gasps ]
[ panting ]
[ panting stops ]
[ coughs , splutters ]
[ chokes , splutters ]
[ phone unlocks ]
[ cat meows ]
[ sirens approaching ]
[ sound fades out ]